[{"id":0,"Title":"Korean Journalist Called ‘Ch*nky’ While Reporting on Jewish Hasidic Community in NYC","Date":"10\/14\/2020","Tags":"['Coronavirus', 'new york city', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Gothamist', 'Borough Park', 'Torah', 'Midwood', 'Brooklyn', 'America', 'Kings County'}","PERSON":"{'Cuomo', 'Kristen Sze', 'Kim', 'Rob Tannenbaum', 'CeFaan Kim', 'Grace Meng ( D-Queens )', 'Zack Fink'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'ABC', 'New York State Assembly', 'NYC', 'Bais Yaakov D ’ Chassidei Gur'}","DATE":"{'October 7 , 2020', 'Oct 13 , 2020', 'Tuesday', 'October 14 , 2020'}","TIME":"{'last night'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/korean-journalist-called-chnky-while-reporting-on-jewish-hasidic-community-in-nyc\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"Bais Yaakov D’Chassidei Gur, 1975 51st St, Brooklyn, NY 11204","lat":40.624723,"lng":-73.977723},{"id":1,"Title":"Asian Grandmother Pushed Onto Subway Tracks, Family Attacked in Brooklyn","Date":"10\/20\/2020","Tags":"['brooklyn', 'elderly']","LOCATION":"{'Brooklyn'}","PERSON":null,"ORGANIZATION":"{'Brooklyn Methodist Hospital'}","DATE":"{'Monday'}","TIME":"{'night', '1:30 p.m.'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/asian-grandmother-pushed-onto-subway-tracks-family-attacked-in-brooklyn\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"Clinton-Washington Avenue subway","lat":40.688092,"lng":-73.96755},{"id":2,"Title":"Anti-Masker Has Meltdown After Thai Family Restaurant Refuses Service in NYC","Date":"11\/4\/2020","Tags":"['anti-mask', 'new york city', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'New York City'}","PERSON":null,"ORGANIZATION":null,"DATE":"{'Nov 3 , 2020'}","TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/anti-masker-rant-refused-service-thai-restaurant-nyc\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"Maple Thai Eatery","lat":40.754533,"lng":-73.925718},{"id":3,"Title":"Trump Supporters Appear to Attack Asian Trump Supporters with Racism at Rally","Date":"11\/9\/2020","Tags":"['donald trump', 'maga', 'new york', 'trump']","LOCATION":"{'Great Neck', 'Long Island', 'New York', 'China', 'Great Neck ?'}","PERSON":"{'Mersedeh Rofeim', 'Mimi Hu', 'Rofeim', 'Donald Trump', 'Shalit', 'Valerie Shalit', 'Rosanna Gao'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'Great Neck Library', '“ Make America Great Again ” ( MAGA', 'Rosanna Gao', 'NextShark', 'Parkwood Sports Complex'}","DATE":"{'November 1 , 2020', '2018', 'Nov. 6', 'Nov. 1', 'Nov 1 , 2020'}","TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/great-neck-trump-supporters-attack-asian-trump-supporters-with-racism-at-rally\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"Parkwood Sports Complex","lat":40.805928,"lng":-73.744559},{"id":4,"Title":"Woman Charged With Hate Crime for Brutally Attacking Muslim Family, Partner Remains at Large","Date":"11\/16\/2020","Tags":"['hate crime', 'new york city', 'Queens']","LOCATION":"{'Queens', 'New York', 'Rego Park'}","PERSON":"{'Neamat Taha'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'Giselle DeJesus', 'Queens Daily Eagle'}","DATE":"{'Nov. 12', 'Nov. 6'}","TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/queens-woman-facing-hate-crimes-for-attacking-muslim-family\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"Rego Park, Queens","lat":40.725572,"lng":-73.862489},{"id":5,"Title":"Gym Owner Dumped by Crossfit After Sending Racist Email to ‘Filthy, Foreign’ Woman","Date":"11\/30\/2020","Tags":"['Coronavirus', 'new york', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'California', 'New York', 'Orchard Park'}","PERSON":"{'Robert Dinero', 'Donald Trump Jr.', 'Joseph Lorigo'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'The Buffalo News', 'Fox News ( Right )', 'Marine', 'CrossFit', 'Fox News'}","DATE":"{'November 23 , 2020', 'November 25 , 2020', 'July'}","TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/orchard-park-gym-owner-racist-profane-email\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"Orchard Park","lat":42.767559,"lng":-78.743919},{"id":6,"Title":"6 Suspects Wanted for Attacking Maskless Asian Woman on NY Subway","Date":"12\/28\/2020","Tags":"['Coronavirus', 'hate crime', 'new york']","LOCATION":"{'Manhattan', 'New York'}","PERSON":null,"ORGANIZATION":"{'NYPD Crime Stoppers', 'Hate Crimes Task Force', 'New York Police Department', 'Americas & West 4 St', 'MTA'}","DATE":"{'December 17 , 2020', 'Dec. 17', 'December 27 , 2020', 'earlier this month', 'December 24 , 2020'}","TIME":"{'1:45 p.m.'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/6-suspects-attack-maskless-asian-woman-new-york-subway\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"6th Ave & West 4th Street, New York, NY 10014","lat":40.731707,"lng":-74.000962},{"id":7,"Title":"‘Go Back to China’: New Jersey Man Faces Hate Crime Charge After Punching Asian Woman","Date":"12\/30\/2020","Tags":"['hate crime', 'Manhattan', 'new york', 'new york city']","LOCATION":"{'Elizabeth', 'New Jersey', 'Manhattan', 'Chelsea', 'China'}","PERSON":"{'Sousa', 'Fred Sousa'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'Lenox Health Greenwich Village', 'Sousa', 'New York Post'}","DATE":"{'Monday'}","TIME":"{'afternoon'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/manhattan-new-jersey-man-hate-crime-punching-asian-woman\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"W 14th St, New York, NY","lat":40.738979,"lng":-74.000663},{"id":8,"Title":"NY Pizza Shop Owners’ Racist Past Against Asian, Black Community Exposed","Date":"1\/11\/2021","Tags":"['new york city', 'pizza', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Los Angeles', 'New York City'}","PERSON":"{'Joe Rosenthal', 'Frank', 'Matthew Famularo', 'Dominic', 'Frank M. ”', 'Rosenthal', 'Frank Moreno', 'Hillary Clinton', 'Dom Moreno'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'Instagram Stories', 'BLM', 'Prince St. Pizza NYC', 'PSP'}","DATE":"{'2016', 'Jan. 8', 'Jan. 7', '2017', 'December'}","TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/prince-street-pizza-owners-step-down\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"27 Prince St A, New York, NY 10012","lat":40.723084,"lng":-73.994528},{"id":9,"Title":"NYC Chef Sparks Outrage for Blaming COVID-19 on Chinese People","Date":"2\/1\/2021","Tags":"['new york', 'new york city', 'nyc', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Second Avenue', 'New York City'}","PERSON":"{'Jose Luis Chavez', 'Chavez'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'Mission Ceviche'}","DATE":"{'Sunday'}","TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/jose-luis-chavez-nyc-chef\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"1400 2nd Ave, New York, NY 10021","lat":40.769101,"lng":-73.957863},{"id":10,"Title":"Asian Man in Critical Condition After Being Stabbed in the Back With a Butcher Knife in NY Chinatown","Date":"2\/26\/2021","Tags":"['assault', 'new york', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Chinatown', 'U.S', 'New York City', 'NYC Chinatown', 'Manhattan', 'New York', 'Brooklyn', 'Bellevue'}","PERSON":"{'Salman Muflihi', 'Daniel Patrick Moynihan', 'Baxter', 'Assemblymember Yuh-Line Niou'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'StopAsianHateCrimes # StopAAPIHate # StopAsianHate', 'Niou', 'Baxter Street and Worth Street', 'Assemblymember Yuh-Line Niou', 'StopAsianHate # StopAAPIHate'}","DATE":"{'January', 'Friday', 'Thursday', 'February 26 , 2021', 'February 26'}","TIME":"{'morning', 'evening', '6:20', '6:15 p.m.'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/chinatown-asian-man-stabbing-new-york\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"Worth St & Baxter St, New York, NY 10007","lat":40.714372,"lng":-74.000477},{"id":11,"Title":"Police Release Footage of Suspect Who Beat 56-Year-Old Asian Man Near Subway","Date":"3\/5\/2021","Tags":"['assault', 'hate crime', 'new york', 'new york city']","LOCATION":"{'Chinatown', 'New York City', 'Malaysia', 'Manhattan', 'East Broadway', 'U.S.'}","PERSON":"{'Teoh Ming Soon'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'E Broadway & Rutgers St', 'New York Post', 'Rutgers Street', 'ABC7 News', 'Pike', 'New York Police Department', 'New York Daily News', 'NYC Health + HospitalsBellevue', 'Rutgers'}","DATE":"{'20 years ago', 'March 4 , 2021', 'Tuesday', 'March 3 , 2021'}","TIME":"{'8:52 p.m.', '8:50 PM'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/subway-video-suspect-attacking-asian-nyc\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"E Broadway & Rutgers St, New York, NY 10002","lat":40.714064,"lng":-73.990195},{"id":12,"Title":"‘Go Back to China!’: Real Estate Agent Loses Job After Racist Rant Caught on Camera","Date":"3\/9\/2021","Tags":"['new york', 'new york city', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Bushwick', 'China', 'Brooklyn', 'New York'}","PERSON":"{'Yang Chen'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'Blink Fitness', 'NextShark', 'StopAsianHateCrimes # StopAAPIHate', '“ Blink Fitness'}","DATE":"{'March 8 , 2021'}","TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/gym-manager-real-estate-agent-fired-nyc\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"Bushwick, Brooklyn","lat":40.695776,"lng":-73.91706},{"id":13,"Title":"‘Chinese Virus!’: Asian Mom Gets Spit On 3 Times While Holding Her Baby in Queens","Date":"3\/12\/2021","Tags":"['attack', 'new york', 'new york city', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Queens', 'Sunnyside', 'Bayside', 'New York'}","PERSON":"{'Peck', 'Grace Meng', 'Sandra Lee', 'Meng'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'Asian Hate Crimes Task Force', 'ABC', 'New York Police Department', 'Korean American Community Services', 'QNS', 'KCS'}","DATE":"{'March 10 , 2021', 'three hours later', 'Tuesday', 'last week'}","TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/queens-chinese-virus-mother-spat-on\/","Type":"COUGH","Address":"186th Street and Peck Avenue, Fresh Meadows NY","lat":40.745162,"lng":-73.790759},{"id":14,"Title":"‘Go Back to Communist China, B*TCH’: Woman Goes on Racist Tirade, Pays Taxi ‘Double’ to Flee Scene","Date":"3\/16\/2021","Tags":"['new york', 'new york city', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'China', 'East'}","PERSON":"{'Daniel Lee'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'Maria Ha', 'NYC Yellow Cab', 'Taxi & Limousine Commission ( TLC', 'New York Police Department', 'NextShark', 'NYPD'}","DATE":"{'March 14'}","TIME":"{'1:25 p.m.'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/racist-nyc-asian-american-communist-china-tirade-taxi-nyc\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"1st Avenue & E 22nd St, New York, NY 10010","lat":40.736225,"lng":-73.979008},{"id":15,"Title":"13-Year-Old Boy Attacked by Teens, Told to ‘Go Back to Your Country’ in Queens","Date":"3\/19\/2021","Tags":"['attack', 'new york', 'new york city', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Queens', 'Bowne Park', 'San Francisco'}","PERSON":null,"ORGANIZATION":"{'NYPD Hate Crime Task Force', 'Google Maps'}","DATE":"{'Tuesday'}","TIME":"{'6:30 p.m.'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/playground-13-year-old-boy-attacked-queens\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"Bowne Park, 29th Ave. & 157th St, Flushing, NY 11354","lat":40.770477,"lng":-73.807205},{"id":16,"Title":"‘Ching Chang Chong’: Asian Woman Calls Out Racist Man, Friend on NYC Subway","Date":"3\/29\/2021","Tags":"['new york', 'new york city', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Wuhan', 'New York'}","PERSON":"{'Nikki C.', 'Nikki', 'Nikki 👻'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'Ching Chong.', 'NextShark', 'Ching Chang Chong.', 'Second Avenue Station'}","DATE":null,"TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/new-york-train-asian-woman-confronts-racist-man\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"2nd Ave, New York, NY 10003","lat":40.723942,"lng":-73.991306},{"id":17,"Title":"Asian 7-Eleven Employee Punched in Possible Hate Crime in NYC","Date":"4\/6\/2021","Tags":"['7-eleven', 'assault', 'hate crime', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'New York'}","PERSON":null,"ORGANIZATION":"{'New York Post', 'NYPD Hate Crimes Task Force', 'New York Police Department', 'CBS New York', 'NYPD'}","DATE":"{'April 3', 'Sunday'}","TIME":"{'night', '6 a.m.'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/asian-7-eleven-employee-punched-in-possible-hate-crime-in-nyc\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"W 39th St & 8th Ave, New York, NY 10018","lat":40.75533,"lng":-73.991177},{"id":18,"Title":"NYC Doormen Who Stood By as Elderly Asian Woman was Beaten Outside Have Been Fired","Date":"4\/6\/2021","Tags":"['assault', 'hate crime', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Kitchen', 'Manhattan', 'New York City'}","PERSON":"{'Elizabeth', 'Brandon Elliot', 'Kari ’', 'Kari', 'Vilma Kari'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'The Brodsky Organization', 'NY Daily News', 'PIX11 News', 'NYPD', 'ABC News'}","DATE":"{'April 6', '2002', 'last Thursday', 'March 30 , 2021', 'March 29'}","TIME":"{'this morning'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/nyc-doormen-filipina-woman-fired\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"360 W 43rd St, New York, NY 10036","lat":40.75867,"lng":-73.991588},{"id":19,"Title":"Undercover Asian NYPD Officer Arrests Woman for Hate Crime After Blaming Salon Workers for COVID","Date":"4\/8\/2021","Tags":"['Coronavirus', 'hate crime', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Chinatown', 'New York City', 'Manhattan', 'New York'}","PERSON":"{'Sharon Williams', 'Dermot Shea'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'” Williams', 'Mayor Bill de Blasio', 'New York Police Department ( NYPD', 'Williams', 'NYPD', 'CBS NewYork', 'StopAsianHate #', 'New York Daily News', 'Sharon Williams'}","DATE":"{'Tuesday', 'April 7 , 2021'}","TIME":null,"Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/undercover-nypd-officer-arrests-woman\/","Type":"VERBAL","Address":"Madison St, New York, NY","lat":40.712526,"lng":-73.991513},{"id":20,"Title":"Man Charged With Hate Crimes for THREE Separate Attacks on Asian New Yorkers","Date":"4\/8\/2021","Tags":"['assault', 'hate crime']","LOCATION":"{'East', 'New York', 'Brooklyn'}","PERSON":"{'Joseph Russo', 'Russo'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'WABC', 'New York Post', 'Kings Highway', 'New York Police Department', 'CBS New York'}","DATE":"{'Monday', 'Wednesday', 'March 5', 'April 8 , 2021', 'March 22'}","TIME":"{'11:15 a.m.'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/man-hate-crimes-three-attacks-ny\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"1406 Avenue U, Brooklyn, NY 11229","lat":40.598651,"lng":-73.957026},{"id":21,"Title":"Bronx Man Arrested For Hate Crime Against Asian Woman","Date":"4\/16\/2021","Tags":"['attack', 'hate crime']","LOCATION":"{'Bronx', 'Manhattan', 'East Side'}","PERSON":"{'Negroni', 'Daniel Negroni'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'1st Ave & E 57th St.', 'StopAsianHateCrimes # StopAsianHate', 'First Avenue', 'Sutton Place', 'CeFaan Kim'}","DATE":"{'Tuesday', 'April 14 , 2021'}","TIME":"{'1 p.m.'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/bronx-man-arrested-hate-crime\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"1st Avenue & E 57th St, New York, NY 10022","lat":40.758314,"lng":-73.962933},{"id":22,"Title":"Man Attacks Undercover Asian Cop, Gets Released Without Bail in New York","Date":"4\/19\/2021","Tags":"['new york', 'new york city', 'racism']","LOCATION":"{'Queens', 'China', 'New York', 'New York Post'}","PERSON":"{'Hernandez', '” Hernandez', 'Juvian Rodriguez', 'Michael Alcazar', 'Rodriguez', 'Ricardo Hernandez'}","ORGANIZATION":"{'NYPD', 'Queens Supreme Court Justice Louis Nock', 'WABC', 'New York Post'}","DATE":"{'Sunday', 'Saturday', 'April 9'}","TIME":"{'5:30 p.m.'}","Url":"https:\/\/nextshark.com\/asian-cop-man-attacks-undercover-new-york\/","Type":"PHYSICAL","Address":"31st St & 39th Ave, Queens, NY 11101","lat":40.752695,"lng":-73.932906}]